Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Projects, 1967-2009; Undated; 1; 118.92 cubic ft.
  - Midwest, 1967-2009; Undated; 1.1
    - Michigan - Detroit City Court Documents, Saulius Deposition, 1989 (Box 19 (1-Projects), Folder 41)
    - Michigan - Detroit City Great Lakes Forum Correspondence, Newsclipping, 1991; Undated (Box 19 (1-Projects), Folder 42)
    - Michigan - Detroit City Wastewater Treatment Plant DMR, 1989-1990 (Box 19 (1-Projects), Folder 43)
    - Michigan - Detroit City Wastewater Treatment Plan PCB Articles, 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Annual Report, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Correspondence, 1984-1985; 1987 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Correspondence, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Court Documents, 1988; 1990 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Newsclipping, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. PCB and Mercury Minimization Program, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 9-11)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. PCB Data Summary, DMR Addendum, 1989-1990 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Permit, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Michigan - Detroit Water & Sewage Dept. Program for Effective Residual Management Correspondence, Sample Data, 1986-1988; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 14-15)
    - Michigan - Elk River United Power, 1998-1999 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Michigan - Federal EPCRA 313 Filers, 1989 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Michigan - Grand Rapids Facility Listing, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Michigan - Grand Rapids Industrial Pretreatment Annual Reports, 1988; 1990-1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Michigan - Grand Rapids Industrial Pretreatment Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Michigan - Grand Trunk Western Railroad Correspondence, Data Sheet, Permit, 1981; 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Michigan - Guardian Photo Inc. Correspondence, Permit, DMR - [RESTRICTED], 1987; 1989-1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Michigan - Hoover Group Inc. Correspondence, Court Documents, Notes, DMR, Permit, 1984-1987; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Michigan - Kalamazoo, City of Correspondence, Annual Report, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Michigan - Kellogg Co. Permit, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Amoco Oil Co. Permit, Data Sheet, 1988; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Coca-Cola Foods Permit, Data Sheet, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities Correspondence, Notes, 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Foremost Insurance Co. Permit, 1989; 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Harvard Industries Permit, Data Sheet, 1987; 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities Listing, 1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Midwest Plating Co., Inc. Correspondence, Data Sheet, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Perrigo Co. Permit, Data Sheet, 1990-1991 (Box 20 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Sealed Power Technologies Permit, Data Sheet, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Silver Leaf Paper Corp. Permit, Data Sheet, Court Document, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Michigan - Minor Facilities, Watervilet Paper Co. Permit, 1987 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Annual Pretreatment Program Status Report, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Permits, 1989; 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System Correspondence, 1991; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System Data Sheets, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System List of Facilities, 1989; 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System Litigation Issues, 1991; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System Monitoring Reports, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 10-11)
    - Michigan - Muskegon County Waste Management System No. 1 Service Agreement, Amendments to Exhibit D, 1985 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Michigan - Owosso City Industrial Pretreatment Program Audit Report, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Michigan - Piconning Industrial Pretreatment Program Audit Report, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Michigan - QNCR, 1988 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Michigan - QNCR, 1989 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Michigan - QNCR, 1990 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Michigan - Waste Type and Quality Summary, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 18-20)
    - Michigan - Williams & Works Operations Data Sheet, 1991 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Minnesota - A. Luster Metal Finishing Correspondence, Notes, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Minnesota - American Crystal Sugar Co. Correspondence, Permit, 1985; 1987; 1990 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Minnesota - Anderson Window Corp. Correspondence, DMR, Permit, 1982-1983; 1986-1987 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Minnesota - Ashland Oil Inc. Correspondence, Notes, EPA Form, Permit, 1981-1987; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Air Permitting Issues, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Compliance Monitoring Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Compliance Sampling Inspection Reports, 1985-1986; 1988 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence, Notes, 1982 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence, Notes, 1983 (Box 21 (1-Projects), Folder 30-31)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1984 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1985 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1986 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1987 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1988 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 5-6)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 7-8)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Data Sheet, 1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. DMR, 1985; 1987-1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Material Data Safety Sheet, 1975-1985; 1988 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Multi-Pathway Health Risk Assessment, Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Permit, 1984-1985 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Permit, 1989-1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Permit and EPA Form, 1982; 1986; 1988 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Permit Expansion Materials, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Sample Analysis, 1987-1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Second Quarter Toxicity Test Results, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Short List for Dioxin, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Site Plan Blueprints, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Wastewater Treatment Plant Evaluation, Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Wastewater Treatment Plant Evaluation Final Report, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Minnesota - Boise Cascade Corp. Water Quality Criterion and Effluent Limitation for Dioxins, 1988 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Minnesota - Brohm Mining Corp. Correspondence and Settlement Agreement, 1993 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Minnesota - Campbell Soup Co. Correspondence and DMR, 1983; 1987; Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Minnesota - Cases, Correspondence, and Notes, 1987-1991; Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Minnesota - Cases, Newsclipplings, Press Release, 1987 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Minnesota - Cases, Pending and Potential, Correspondence, and Notes, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Minnesota - Circuit Board 1, Inc. Correspondence, Notes and Permit, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Minnesota - Circuit Board 1, Inc. Stipulation Agreement, 1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - Minnesota - Container Graphics Corp. Manifest Inspection Data, 1987-1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - Minnesota - Curtis Electronics Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1986-1991 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - Minnesota - Curtis Electronics Corp. DMR and Permit, 1984; 1987; 1989-1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - Minnesota - Curtis Electronics Corp. Stipulation Agreements, 1990 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - Minnesota - Crystal Cabinet Works, Inc. Annual Report Form for Generation of Hazardous Waste, 1988-1989 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - Minnesota - Deep Draw Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1985; 1988-1991 (Box 22 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - Minnesota - Deep Draw Corp. Permit, DMR, Inspection Report, 1985-1991 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Design Fabricated Parts Inc. Manifest Inspection Data, 1987-1990 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Minnesota - Elk River Generating Station Correspondence Permit, DMR, 1996-1999 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Minnesota - Etchit Inc. Correspondence, Notes, Permit, DMR, 1987-1990 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Minnesota - Etchit Inc. Stipulation Agreement, 1990 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Minnesota - Funding of Environmental Rights Proposals December 12, 1987 Meeting (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Minnesota - Gampers Chrome Plating Inc. Correspondence, Permit, and DMR, 1988-1990 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Minnesota - George A. Hormel & Co. Correspondence, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Minnesota - George A. Hormel & Co. Court Documents, 1987-1988 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Minnesota - George A. Hormel & Co. Permit and DMR, 1984; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Minnesota - Hennepin County Evaluation of Proposal Mass Incineration Plant, 1987 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Minnesota - Hennepin County Mass Incineration Plant Correspondence, Notes and Newsclippings, 1981-1987; Undated (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Minnesota - Hennepin County Testimony of Morries, 1987 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Minnesota - Hennepin Paper Co. DMR and Permit, 1989-1991 (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Minnesota - Jacob Schmidt Brewing Co. Correspondence and Permit, 1983; 1987; Undated (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Correspondence and Permit, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1993, 1993 July (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 18-19)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1993, 1994 January (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 20-23)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1994, 1994 April (Box 23 (1-Projects), Folder 24-26)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1995, 1994 April (Box 24 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1994, 1994 July (Box 24 (1-Projects), Folder 2-6)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1994, 1994 October (Box 24 (1-Projects), Folder 7-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1994 Vol. 1, 1995 January (Box 24 (1-Projects), Folder 13-14)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1994 Vol. 2, 1995 January (Box 24 (1-Projects), Folder 15-17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1995 Vol. 1, 1995 April (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 1-2)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1995 Vol. 2, 1995 April (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 3-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1995 Vol. 1, 1995 July (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1995 Vol. 2, 1995 July (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 8-10)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1995 Vol. 1, 1996 January (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 11-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1995 Vol. 2, 1996 January (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 13-15)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1996 Vol. 1, 1996 April (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 16-17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1996 Vol. 2, 1996 April (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1996 Vol. 1, 1996 July (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1996 Vol. 2, 1996 July (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 6-8)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1996 Vol. 1, 1996 October (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 9-10)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1996 Vol. 2, 1996 October (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 11-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1996 Vol.1, 1997 January (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 13-15)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1996 Vol.2, 1997 January (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 16-17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1996 Vol.2, 1997 January (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1997 Vol. 1, 1997 April (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 2-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1997 Vol. 2, 1997 April (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 4-6)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1997 Vol. 1, 1997 July (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 7-8)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1997 Vol. 2, 1997 July (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 9-11)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1997 Vol 1., 1997 October (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 12-13)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1997 Vol 2., 1997 October (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 14-16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1997 Vol. 1, 1998 January (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 17-18)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1997 Vol. 1, 1998 January (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1997 Vol. 2, 1998 January (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 2-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1998 Vol.1, 1998 April (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1998 Vol.2, 1998 April (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1998 Vol. 1, 1998 July (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 8-9)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1998 Vol. 2, 1998 July (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 10-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1998 Vol. 1, 1998 October (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 13-14)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1998 Vol. 2, 1998 October (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 15-16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1998 Vol. 1, 1998 January (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1998 Vol. 2, 1998 January (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1999 Vol. 1, 1999 April (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 1999 Vol. 2, 1999 April (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 6-8)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1999, 1999 July (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 9-10)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 1999 Vol. 2, 1999 July (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 11-13)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1999 Vol. 1, 1999 October (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 1999 Vol. 2, 1999 October (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 15-17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1999 Vol. 1, 2000 January (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1999 Vol. 1, 2000 January (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 1999 Vol. 2, 2000 January (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 2-4)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 2000 Vol. 1, 2000 April (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 2000 Vol. 2, 2000 April (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 6-8)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 2000, 2000 July (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 2000 Vol. 2, 2000 July (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 10-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 2000 Vol. 1, 2000 October (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 13-14)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 2000 Vol. 2, 2000 October (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 15-17)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 2000 Vol 1., 2001 January (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 2000 Vol 1., 2001 January (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 4th Q. 2000 Vol 2., 2001 January (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 2-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 2001 Vol. 1, 2001 April (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 1st Q. 2001 Vol. 2, 2001 April (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 2001 Vol 1., 2001 July (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 8-9)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 2nd Q. 2001 Vol 2., 2001 July (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 10-11)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report 3rd Q. 2001, 2001 October (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 12-15)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2001, 2002 January (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2001, 2002 January (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2002, 2002 April (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 4-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 2nd Q. 2002, 2002 July (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 8-11)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 3rd Q. 2002, 2002 October (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 12-15)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2002, 2003 January (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2002, 2003 January (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2003 Vol. 1, 2003 April (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2003 Vol. 2, 2003 February (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 2nd Q. 2003, 2003 July (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 8-11)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 3rd Q. 2003, 2003 October (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 12-15)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2003, 2004 January (Box 33 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2003, 2004 January (Box 34 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2004, 2004 April (Box 34 (1-Projects), Folder 4-7)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 2nd Q. 2004, 2004 July (Box 34 (1-Projects), Folder 8-10)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 3rd Q. 2004, 2004 October (Box 34 (1-Projects), Folder 11-13)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2004, 2005 January (Box 34 (1-Projects), Folder 14-16)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2005, 2005 April (Box 35 (1-Projects), Folder 1-3)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 2nd Q. 2005, 2005 July (Box 35 (1-Projects), Folder 4-6)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 3rd Q. 2005, 2005 October (Box 35 (1-Projects), Folder 7-9)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 4th Q. 2005, 2006 January (Box 35 (1-Projects), Folder 10-12)
    - Minnesota - Koch Refining Co. Consent Order Quarterly Report, Flint Hills Resources 1st Q. 2006, 2006 April (Box 35 (1-Projects), Folder 13-15)